Guide to the Nathaniel Tarn Papers, ca. 1939-2000 M1132
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 6. Accession 2011-046
  - Correspondence and Ephemera
    - Olson, Toby, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Peck, John, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Phillips, Dennis, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Phillips, Dennis, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Phillips, Dennis, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Phillips, Dennis, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Phillips, Dennis, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Presidential Inaugural Committee: Invitation to 2009 United States Presidential Inauguration (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Quarterm, Peter, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Reactions to "Mathis At Issenheim" Poem, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Rodney, Janet, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Rodney, Janet, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome, 2010 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Rothenberg, Michael, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Rudolf, Anthony, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Nathaniel Tarn "Slope", 2010 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Smolny College, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Da Souza, Luis, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Da Souza, Luis, 2010, 2011 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Tarn, Nathaniel: Ephemera and Correspondence, 1965, 1984, 2000-2002 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Tarn, Nathaniel: Ephemera and Correspondence, 1963, 1968, 1978, 2002-2009 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Tejada, Roberto, 2006 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Tejada, Roberto, 2007 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Tejada, Roberto, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Tranter, John, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Tranter, John, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Weinberger, Eliot, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Weinberger, Eliot, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Weinberger, Eliot, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Weinberger, Eliot, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Weinberger, Eliot, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Yepez, Heriberto, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Yepez, Heriberto, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Zamir, Shamoon, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Zamir, Shamoon, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Zamir, Shamoon, 2008 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Zamir, Shamoon, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Zamir, Shamoon, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Nathaniel Tarn: Miscellaneous Drafts and Manuscript (Unpublished as of 10/2011)
    - Drafts, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Drafts, 2006, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Drafts, 2008, 2010 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - The Persephones, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Drafts, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Recollections of Being (Poems 1988-1998) (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Recollections of Being (Poems 1988-1998) (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Drafts, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Drafts, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript for [Amazonia], 2009/2010 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: Miscellaneous Proofs
      - Nathaniel Tarn: Proofs, 2008 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - The Embattled Lyric Essays and Conversations in Poetics and Anthropology, Corrected Publisher Proof (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - 'Embattled Lyric' Proofs (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - 'Embattled Lyric' Proofs (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Nathaniel Tarn Proofs, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Nathaniel Tarn Proofs, 2007, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Nathaniel Tarn Proofs, 2008, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Photographs
    - Photographs (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nathaniel Tarn Poems Published On Web
    - Nathaniel Tarn Poems Published On Web, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Nathaniel Tarn Poems Published On Web, 2007 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nathaniel Tarn: Materials Related to Reading Engagements
    - Nathaniel Tarn Materials and Ephemera Related to Reading Engagements, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn Email Related to Reading Engagements, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Nathaniel Tarn, Reviews of
    - Nathaniel Tarn, Reviews of, 2006 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Nathaniel Tarn, Reviews of, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Nathaniel Tarn, Reviews of, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Nathaniel Tarn, Reviews of, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Web Pages Related to Nathaniel Tarn
    - Web Pages Related to Nathaniel Tarn, 2008 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Web Pages Related to Nathaniel Tarn, 2009 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Web Pages Related to Nathaniel Tarn, 2010 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Nathaniel Tarn's Journals, Daybooks, and Day Planners
    - Nathaniel Tarn Journals: Australia (August 23, 2006 - August 30, 2006) and Papua New Guinea (August 7, 2006 - August 23, 2006) (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Nathaniel Tarn's Daybook (January 3, 2005 - January 20, 2009) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Nathaniel Tarn's Day Planners (2005, 2006) (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Nathaniel Tarn's Day Planners (2007) (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn's Day Planners (2008) (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Nathaniel Tarn's Day Planner and Daybook (2009) (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Nathaniel Tarn's Day Planners (2010) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Avia
    - Avia Drafts (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Avia: Reviews and Correspondence from Peter Quartermain (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Avia: Correspondence and Ephemera Regarding Avia (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Avia: Corrected Typescript (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Books and Serials
    - Tarn, Nathaniel. Chamans Et Prêtres Au Guatemala Dans La Région Du Lac Atitlán: Scandales Dans La Maison Des Oiseaux. Paris: L'Harmattan, 2006. Print. (Box 14, Item 1)
    - Berge, H C. Op Een Mat Van Gele Veren: Poëzievertalingen 1968-2003. Amsterdam: Athenaeum-Polak & Van Gennep, 2005. Print. (Box 14, Item 2)
    - Mackey, Nathaniel. Hambone 17 [Santa Cruz, CA., etc.]. (Box 14, Item 3)
    - The New Review of Literature. Los Angeles, CA: Graduate Writing Program of Otis College of Art & Design, April 2006. Print. (Box 14, Item 4)
    - Talisman: A Journal of Contemporary Poetry and Poetics. Hoboken, NJ: Talisman, Summer/Autumn 2010. Print. (Box 14, Item 5)
    - Görtschacher, Wolfgang. Poetry Salzburg Review. Salzburg, Austria: W. Görtschacher, Dept. of English and American Studies, University of Salzburg, Spring 2010. Print. (Box 14, Item 6)
    - Po&sie. Paris: Librairie Classique Eugène Belin, 128-129. (Box 14, Item 7)
    - Tears in the Fence. Dorset (c/o D. Caddy, 12 Hod View, Stourpaine, Nr. Blandford Forum, Dorset DT11 8TN: s.n., Autumn 2010. Print. (Box 14, Item 8)
    - Sartorius, Joachim, and Richard Dove. Ice Memory: Selected Poems. Manchester: Carcanet, 2006. Print. (Box 14, Item 9)
    - Damn the Caesars. Montague, NJ: Punch Press, 2007. Print. (Box 14, Item 10)
    - Ozzard, Chris, and Jeremy Hilton. Fire. Malvern, England: Fire, March 2008. Print. (Box 14, Item 11)
    - Berge, H C. Een Beeld Van De Zinnen. Nieuwe Doelen, 2008. (Box 14, Item 12)
    - The Poker. Cambridge, MA: The Poker, Summer 2004. Print. (Box 14, Item 13)
    - Morrow, Bradford. Conjunctions: Bi-annual Volumes of New Writing. Annandale-on-Hudson, NY: Bard College, 2007. Print. (Box 14, Item 14)
    - First Intensity: A Magazine of New Writing. Lawrence: First Intensity, Fall 2006. Print. (Box 14, Item 15)
    - Notre Dame Review: Icons & Incomings. 24 Summer/Fall 2007. Print. (Box 14, Item 16)
    - Aridjis, Homero, Betty Ferber, and George McWhirter. Eyes to See Otherwise: Selected Poems = Ojos, De Otro Mirar. New York: New Directions, 2002. Print. (Box 14, Item 17)
    - Saint Elizabeth Street. Brooklyn, NY: Saint Elizabeth Street Press, Spring 2004. Print. (Box 14, Item 18)
    - Rich, David, and Lisa R. Rich. Process. Gloucester, Mass: Process, July 2008. Print (Box 14, Item 19)
    - Eleven Eleven: Cca Literary Arts Journal. San Francisco, CA: California College of the Arts, 2008. Print. (Box 14, Item 20)
    - Frazer, Tony. Shearsman. Plymouth, Devon, England: Shearsman, Spring/Summer 2008. Print (Box 14, Item 21)
    - First Intensity: A Magazine of New Writing. Lawrence: First Intensity, Fall 2007. Print. (Box 14, Item 22)
    - Pease, Roland. Zoland Poetry. Hanover, NH: Zoland Books, 2009. Print. (Box 14, Item 23)
    - Golden Handcuffs Review. Vashon, WA: Golden Handcuffs Review, Spring-Summer 2009. Print (Box 14, Item 24)
    - Rockefeller Foundation. Bellagio Study and Conference Center Lake Como, Italy. 1988 Annual Report. (Box 14, Item 25)
    - Tears in the Fence. Dorset (c/o D. Caddy, 12 Hod View, Stourpaine, Nr. Blandford Forum, Dorset DT11 8TN: s.n., Summer 2009. Print. (Box 14, Item 26)
  - Scandals in the House of Birds
    - An Abundance of Waters, Corrected Typescript (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Scandals in the House of Birds Typescript (Starting from Chapter Eighteen) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Experimental Writing Schemata for Scandals in the House of Birds (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Scandals in the House of Birds: Related Material (1 of 4) (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Scandals in the House of Birds: Related Material (2 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Scandals in the House of Birds: Related Material (3 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Scandals in the House of Birds: Related Material (4 of 4) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - CDs: Miscellaneous Readings
    Access to Collection
    The materials are open for research use. Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
    - WordTemple with Katherine Hastings: Nathaniel Tarn [Jane Hirshfield] (Box 14, Compact disc 1)
    - Remembering Gene: A Memorial Reading of Gene Frunkin's Poetry, 3/30/2007 (Box 14, Compact disc 2)
    - Nathaniel Tarn Reads at Acequia Booksellers, 9/7/2008 (Box 14, Compact disc 3)
    - Janet Rodney Reads, 10/5/2008 (Box 14, Compact disc 4)
    - Nathaniel Tarn Reading, Acequia Books, 9/7/2008 (Box 14, Compact disc 5)
    - Nathaniel Tarn and a Couple Canadians at the Living Batch 1990 Albuquerque (Box 14, Compact disc 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn and Tony Frazer at Devon Bird of Prey Center, 6/2008 (Box 14, Compact disc 7)
    - The Postman (Il Postino) CD, with Pablo Neruda Poems (Box 14, Compact disc 8)
- Series 7. Accession 2011-111
  This accession consists of Avia-related materials, Tarn's Ph.D. Thesis, miscellaneous teaching materials/notes, and reel to reel films.
  - Avia
    - Avia: Bibliographic Index Cards (Box 1)
    - Avia: Pilot Rod Smith, RAF: Related Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Avia: Pilot Rod Smith, RAF: Related Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Avia: Pilot Rod Smith, RAF: Related Correspondence and Ephemera (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Avia: Aircraft Data (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Avia: Lindbergh (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Avia: Lindbergh Weather (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Avia: Lindbergh Weather and Routing (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Avia: Lindbergh Weather and Routing (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Avia: Lindbergh, Notes and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Avia: Lindbergh, Notes and Manuscript (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Avia: Lindbergh, Notes and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Avia: Battle of Britain [Corrected typescript] (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Avia: Battle of Britain [Corrected typescript] (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Avia: Notes and Ephemera (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Avia: Malta Research (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Avia: Corrected Typescript Chapter IV - IX (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Avia: Drafts (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Avia: Russia Research (1 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Avia: Russia Research (2 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Avia: Russia Research (3 of 3) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Avia: Manuscript and Typescript (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Avia: Flight Logs, Bader (Half-box 5, Folder 1)
    - Avia: Partial Manuscript and Partial Typescript (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Avia: Partial Typescript (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Avia: Proofs For Final (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Avia: Proofs For Final (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Avia: Proofs For Final (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Nathaniel Tarn's Miscellaneous Manuscripts and Notes
    - Typescript of Unpublished Draft Essay on the Language Poets (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Notes on Various Critics (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Notes on Blake and Dante (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Notes on Vocal and Choral (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Notes on William Carlos Williams (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Notes on Buddhist Studies (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Notes on Ezra Pound and Other Poets (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Tzutujil Lessons, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Nathaniel Tarn's Ph.D. Thesis (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Nathaniel Tarn's Teaching Materials
    - Maya Teaching Materials (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Maya Teaching Materials (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Teaching in China Materials (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Teaching Notes on American Poets (For Russia) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Nathaniel Tarn's Research Orders/Requests For Various Journals, Documents, and Catalogs (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Reel to Reel Film
    - David Lenfest "The Great Odor of Summer." (Boxes 10, Item 1)
    - Nathaniel Tarn Film of Santiago Atitlans, Guatemala, 1952-1953 (16mm) (Box 10, Item 2)
    - Yatanaku, Burma 1959, and Marc 2/13/1966 (Box 10, Item 3)
    - Possible Recording of Taungbyon Nat (Spirit) Festival North of Mandalay, Burma, circa 1959 - indicates unique material. (Box 10, Item 4)
    - Unmarked, unknown footage (Box 10, Item 5)
    - Unmarked, unknown footage (Box 10, Item 6)
- Series 8. Non-literary publications
  - Publications regarding Alaska and conservation efforts (Box 1)
  - Publications regarding Alaska and conservation efforts (Box 2)
- Series 9. Accession 2015-025, 2011-2014; 5.21 Linear Feet Contents include paper correspondence files (printed from email), diaries and notebooks, manuscripts and typescripts of works and print copies of published works by Nathaniel Tarn. The folder listing is as provided by creator, organized by year from 2011-2014.
  - Correspondence and ephemera, 2011
    - 2011 General (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Anthropology (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Nathanial Tarn: drafts (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: prose (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: publishing (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: reviews (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: web (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Avia (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - Wikipedia (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - United Kingdom (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Latin America (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Auxemery, Jean Paul (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - Bartlett, Lee and Jennifer Bartlett (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Bouchard, Dan (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Brandi, John (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Campbell, Carolee (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Deming, Richard (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Donahue, Joseph (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Feinsod, Harris (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Fong, Monique (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Heller, Mike (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Hill, Barry (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Hillman, Brenda (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Irby, Ken (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Kelly, Robert (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Lamb, Joe (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Lewsis, Ruark (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Lorrain, Philippe H. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Murdock, Peter (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Newman, Denise (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - O'Leary, Peter (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Olson, Toby (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Phillips, Dennis (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Rodney, Janet (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Souza, Luis de (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Weinberger, Eliot (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Yepez, Heriberto (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Zamir, Shamoon (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Alaska 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
    - Old Stuff (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Conference progra: One Makes Many: a conference of poetic interactions, November 2011 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: publications (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence and ephemera, 2012
    - 2012 General (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
    - Anthropology (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: drafts (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: publishing (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: Avia (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: Gondwanka 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: Midwest (Box 4, Folder 10-11)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: VIF book (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Auxemery, Jean Paul (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Bartlett, Lee and Jennifer Bartlett (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Benson, Christopher (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Bouchard, Dan (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Brandi, John (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Campbell, Carolee (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Deming, Richard (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Donahue, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Feinsod, Harris (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Fong, Monique (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Hill, Barry (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Hill, Lindsay (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Hillman, Brenda (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Kearns, Cleo (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Lamb, Joe (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Lewis Ruark (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Murdock, Patrick (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Newman, Denise (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - O'Leary, Peter (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Phillips, Dennis (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Quartermain, Peter (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Rodney, Janet (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Rodney, Janet: Art (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Shimoda, Brandon (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Sousa, Luis de (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Weinberger, Eliot (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Old stuff (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
    - Partial manuscript (typed) (Box 6, Folder 3-4)
    - Pocket diaries, 2011-2012 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: diary from Ecuador, May 8-25, 2010 and January 22-February 8, 2011; Calendar 2011 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: diary from Antarctica, January 5-February 1, 2008; Calendar 2012 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - or, spring 2012: Nathaniel Tarn's review article on Dennis Phillips' Hope (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Publications: edited by Nathaniel Tarn and with his works (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Correspondence and ephemera, 2013
    - Autoanthropology, one (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 2013 General (Box 7, Folder 4-6)
    - Anthropology (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: drafts (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: proofs (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: prose (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: publishing (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: reviews (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: web (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Auxemery, Jean Paul (Box 8, Folder 8-9)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Benson, Chris (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Brandi, John (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Campbell, Carolee (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Corngold, Stanley (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Deming, Richard (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Deverse, Kurt (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Donahue, Joseph (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Feinsod, Harris (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Fong, Monique (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Heller, Michael (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Hill, Barry (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Hill, Linsay (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Hillman, Brenda (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Hofer, Matt (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Kearns, Cleo (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Lamb, Joe (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Lewis, Ruark (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Lorrain, Phiippe (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Mackey, Nate (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Murdock, Patrick (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Newman, Denise (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - O'Leary, Peter (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - O'Brien, Geoffrey (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Olson, Toby (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Phillips, Dennis (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Rodney, Janet (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Quartermain, Peter (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Shimoda, Brandon (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Ten berge, H. C. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Weinberger, Eliot (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Zamir, Shamoon (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Old stuff (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Pocket diaries, 2012-2013 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Publications with Nathaniel Tarn's works (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: proofs (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence and ephemera, 2014
    - Autoanthropology two: typescript, unpublished (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - 2014 General (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - Anthropology (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: Avia (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Lady Robby Dundas (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: drafts (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: publishing (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: proofs (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: reviews (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: web (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Auxemery, Jean Paul (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Bartlett, Jennifer (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Benson, Christopher (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Bouchard, Daniel (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Brandi, John (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Campbell, Carolee (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Deming, Richard (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Deverese, Kurt (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Digby, John (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Donahue, Joseph (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Gander, Forrest (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Heller, Michael (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Hill, Barry (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Hill, Lindsay (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Hillman, Brenda (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Hinton, David (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Hofer, Matt (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Kearns, Cleo (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Lamb, Joe (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Macniven, Ian S. (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Murdock, Patrick (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Myers, Joan (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - O'Leary, Peter (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Olson, Toby (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Phillips, Dennks (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Quartermain, Peter (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Rodney Janet (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Rothenberg, Jerome (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Schelling, Andrew (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Shimoda, Brandon (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Souza, Luis de (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Subin, Anna della (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Ten Berge, H. C. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Ten Berge, H. C. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Weinberger, Eliot (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Zamir, Shamon (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Zhang, Ziqing (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Old stuff (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Photographs: Montreal International Poetry Conference, September 1967. CD of Nathaniel Tarn reading at METAL, Ann Arbor, Michigan, May 4, 2012. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Academic career (Box 12, Folder 14-15)
    - Robert Salkeld: patent applications, 2008-2014 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Engagement calendar, 2013 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Nathaniel Tarn: publications (Half-box 13)